

PROFILE 90s child, I grew up with the Internet. Since then, I have always been fascinated by the web and its architecture. To satisfy my creativity and curiosity, I naturally turned to digital communication. After 4 years, I decided to learn a new complementary skill. I am now a junior front-end developer & digital communication manager.

# **EXPERIENCES**

### **HEAD OF DIGITAL COMMUNICATION**

August 2018 - March 2022

# French Apples & Pears Association, Toulouse FR

In charge of digital development for the french label Vergers écoresponsables (apples, pears, peaches, apricots)

### **DIGITAL COMMUNICATION**

Development of the label's social media strategy with the following objectives: visibility & brand awareness

### **COMMUNITY MANAGEMENT / CONTENT CREATION**

Creation of editorial schedules, content writing, graphic design, managing and moderating social medias, setting up paid campaigns and drafting of performance reports

#### **MEDIA WATCH**

Curation of written, audiovisual and digital press for the members' weekly press review

#### OTHERS

Website animation, social media training, photography, video capture and editing

# **COMMUNITY MANAGER**

February 2017 - February 2018

### Agence Pure, Toulouse FR

In charge of digital development and social media strategy

#### **DIGITAL COMMUNICATION**

Development of the digital strategy for 7 clients

## **COMMUNITY MANAGEMENT / CONTENT CREATION**

Managing and moderating social medias with creation of editorial schedules, content writing, setting up paid campaigns and drafting of performance reports

## **SKILLS**

**HARD SKILLS** Ruby • Rails • ES6 • JS • SQL • Sass HTML • CSS • Bootstrap • Wireframing (Figma, Sketch) Suite Adobe (Ps, Ae, Pr) • Graphic Design • Social Medias

**SOFT SKILLS** Product Mindset • UX/UI Basics Collaboration Workflows • Curious • Creative • Team spirit Project management • Content management • Analyze

# **PROJECTS**

# **REMPIL - RoR app**

March 2022

### Le Wagon, Full Stack Bootcamp

We made an application as part of our end of bootcamp project for Rempil: a turnkey solution for reusable containers

# **ROYAL PARTY - RoR website**

March 2022

### Le Wagon, Full Stack Bootcamp

We made a "Airbnb clone" project called Royal Party where you can rent castles for your private events

### **AHELE**

September 2019 - June 2021

## Founder, Toulouse FR

Ahele was an online store for women

# **EDUCATION**

# **FULL STACK BOOTCAMP**

October 2021 - March 2022

Le Wagon, 100% remote

# MASTER DIGITAL CONTENT MANAGEMENT

2014 - 2016

EJCAM, Marseille FR

# BACHELOR'S DEGREE PROJECT MANAGEMENT

2011 - 2014

ICT, Toulouse FR

# **LANGUAGES**

FRENCH + ENGLISH

C1

### **GERMAN**

A1